McCaddon Collection of the Barnum and Bailey Circus, 1871-1907 (bulk 1895-1905): Finding Aid TC040
Manuscripts Division
- Series 1: Photographs, 1854-1903; 16 boxes; 8 items
  - Performers I, 1871-1898; 3 boxes
    - Ament and Nichelson, Chicago, Ill., dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 97)
    - Unidentified man in Indian costume with hatchet and rifle, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 98)
    - Bartlett Family (3) sharpshooters, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 99)
    - Florence Bartlett, child sharpshooter, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 100)
    - Capt. A.H. Bogardus, Champion Wing Shot, 1871-1888; 1 item (Box 6, Item 101)
    - Capt. A.H. Bogardus & Sons, Chamption Shots of the World, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 6, Item 102-103)
    - Henry Bogardus, sharpshooter, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 104)
    - Edward Bogardus, sharpshooter, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 6, Item 105-106)
    - Unidentified man in costume with rifle (Capt. Bogardus?), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 107)
    - Rio Grande Bill, sharpshooter, rope artist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 108)
    - Carmen Alnorez, rope artist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 109)
    - Melrose Family, cyclists, Barrett's Circus, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 110)
    - Willmot & Sewell, cyclists, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 111)
    - George French's Troupe, cyclists, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 112)
    - Unidentified female cyclist (Polly Elliott?), dates not examined; 3 items (Box 6, Item 113-115)
      See No. 86
    - Unidentified male cyclist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 116)
    - Troupe Mayo, American Roller Skaters (3), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 117)
    - Unidentified roller skating troupe (5), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 118)
    - Andy Sweeney, strongman, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 119)
      See no. 23&28.
    - Unidentified strongman, same as no. 20, dates not examined; 3 items (Box 6, Item 120-122)
    - E. Naustie (strongman?), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 123)
    - Pete Courchini, Court Jester, Cooper & Bailey Shows, Australia, 1876-1877; 1 item (Box 6, Item 124)
    - Oscar Lee, clown, animal trainer, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 125)
    - "Idola, the Lion Queen", lion tamer, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 126)
    - Mustang Ned, Champion Fancy and Trick rider, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 127)
    - Unidentified man in cowboy suit and chaps, holding shotgun, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 128)
    - Mrs. Fritz, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 129)
      See no. 89.
    - Damm Family (4) musicians, three violins, one cello, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 130)
    - Unidentified man, playing autoharp, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 131)
    - Unidentified man, in band uniform, with trombone, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 132)
    - Nelson Sinclair, slack-wire artist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 133)
    - Vaidis Twin Sisters, aerialists, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 134)
    - Deirl, Acrobat, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 135)
    - Female contortionist and male clown act, unidentified, dates not examined; 4 items (Box 6, Item 136-139)
    - Japanese Wrestlers, Anna Kitchu & Assu Toru, Yokohawa, Japan, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 140)
    - Mrs. Augusta Ordey of "The Ordeys" Hungarian Balancers and Jugglers, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 141)
      See no. 17.
    - Unidentified man, balancing spinning plates, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 142)
    - Prince Tanaka of "Prince and Princess Tanaka, Genuine Oriental Wonders" jugglers, 1892; 1 item (Box 6, Item 143)
    - Princess Tanaka, see above, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 144)
    - Oriental juggler (Prince Tanaka?), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 145)
    - Andersens, the Cannon King, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 146)
    - Barnello, "The Man with the Breath of Fire,", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 147)
      See no. 36
    - "Kii-Kii" glass dancer, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 148)
    - Japanese wrestler, Annakitchu & Assutoru, Yokohawa, Japan, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 149)
      See no. 150
    - Elephantine Colossus, building in shape of elephant, West Brighton Beach, Coney Island, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 150)
    - Harding & Ali-Sid, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 6, Item 151)
    - Leonard Lewis and two trained mules, clown and animal trainer, dates not examined; 8 items (Box 6, Item 152-159)
  - Performers II, 1854-1897; 3 boxes
    - Largard Trp. Diable Acrobates, acrobats in devil costumes, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 1)
      See no. 28
    - Senorita Geraldina y La Nina del Aire, Aerialists, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 2)
    - Sisters Reisley (3), flying gymnasts, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 3)
    - Familia Canadas, gymnasts, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 4)
    - William Bickett of "The Bicketts" (Minnie), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 5)
    - Leopold, acrobat, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 6)
    - Miss Apolonia, "Great Tight Wire Act", dates not examined; 4 items (Box 7, Item 7-10)
    - William Irwin, trapeze artist, aerial equilibrist, dates not examined; 3 items (Box 7, Item 11-13)
    - Millie Irwin (wife of William) "Female Samson", "Iron Jaw Act", dates not examined; 2 items (Box 7, Item 14-15)
    - Las Aquilas (2), gymnasts, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 16)
    - Nelson Sinclair, slack-wire artist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 17)
      See Box II, no. 143.
    - Frank La Rosa, gymnast, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 18)
    - Frank La Rosa, "French Ring Act", gymnast, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 19)
    - Mlle. Irene (Mrs. John Leslie) aerialist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 20)
    - Sisters Lawrence, gymnasts and flying trapeze artists, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 21)
    - Joseph Cassim, acrobat, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 22)
    - Sisters Pontelli, aerial and acrobatic act, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 23)
    - Family Elbin, acrobatic artists to the Imperial Family in Russia, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 24)
    - Albion Family (William, Ettie, Willie) acrobats, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 25)
    - Nestor & Venoa of Royal Aquarium, London, England, gymnasts, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 26)
    - James Irwin, acrobat, aerialist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 27)
    - Lagard Troupe, Diables Acrobates, acrobats, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 28)
      See no. 1
    - Unidentified male acrobat, gymnast, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 29)
    - Miss Zarah Ceballos, "La Verdadera Peyna del Aire" Aerialist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 30)
    - Frank la Mondue, slack wire artist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 31)
    - William and Minnie Bickett of "The Bicketts", aerialists, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 32)
      See no. 5.
    - Minnie Bickett, aerialist, see above, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 33)
    - James Irwin (doing a head balance), acrobat, aerialist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 34)
      See no. 2
    - Teodulo con el celebre, Nicolas Ceballos, acrobats, aerialists, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 35)
    - Teodulo R. Ceballos, aerialist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 36)
    - Nicolas Ceballos, aerialist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 37)
    - Zarah Ceballos, aerialist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 38)
      See nos. 30 & 35
    - Lawrence M. Donovan "Hero of Niagara Falls" champion Jumper of the World, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 39)
    - William Betcheler, Champion Leaper, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 40)
    - John I. Crossley of "Crossley & Elder, Athletes", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 41)
    - M. and Madame Rofix "Dans leurs Creations", photo depiction of their feats, balancing act, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 7, Item 42)
    - George Testo of "Testo and Onri", a strongman act, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 7, Item 43-44)
    - Fanny Onri of "Testo and Onri", a strongman act, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 7, Item 45-46)
    - Iman A. Caicedo, acrobat, gymnast? Empire Theatre, London, 1889; 3 items (Box 7, Item 47-49)
    - Unidentified girl, gymnast, acrobat, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 7, Item 50-51)
    - Unidentified girl, gymnast, acrobat, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 52)
    - Unidentified two male trapeze artists and one clown on trapeze rigging, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 53)
    - Unidentified male, strong man or gymnast?, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 54)
    - 'Harry' Cee-Mee (Joseph Henry Fortman), trapeze artist or acrobat, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 55)
    - Larry Le Roy, trapeze artist or acrobat?, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 56)
    - William Edwards, trapeze artist or acrobat?, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 57)
    - Two unidentified males, back to back, trapeze artists and acrobats, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 58)
    - Unidentified male, gymnast or aerialist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 59)
    - Two unidentified females with fans and parasols, high wire act?, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 60)
    - Unidentified male, aerialist or acrobat?, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 61)
    - Barlow and De Vere (2), aerialists/acrobats, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 62)
    - Zarah F. Ceballos, aerialist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 63)
      See nos. 30, 35, 38
    - Adelaide & Lillian, acrobats or aerialists?, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 64)
    - L. Girots & Fils (4), acrobats or aerialists?, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 65)
    - Charles Clarker, aerialist or acrobat?, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 66)
    - Rose Julian, acrobat or aerialist?, dates not examined; 3 items (Box 8, Item 67-69)
    - Miss Blanche Edwards, aerialist or acrobat?, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 70)
    - Unidentified woman, aerialist or acrobat, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 71)
    - Lucy Davine, aerialist or acrobat?, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 72)
    - Miss Leoville, equestrian and equilibrist of Transfield's Circus in the UK, circa 1893-1900; 1 item (Box 8, Item 73)
    - Unidentified woman, aerialist or acrobat, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 74)
    - Unidentified couple, aerialists or acrobats, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 75)
    - Unidentified couple, aerialists or acrobats, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 76)
    - Four male clowns, dressed as devils, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 77)
    - Joseph Leon, original silent clown, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 78)
    - Harry Wentworth, Principal Clown, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 79)
      See no. 91
    - Mr. Whitfield, entertainer, impersonator, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 80)
    - Marie Wartenberg, acrobat, contortionist, dates not examined; 4 items (Box 8, Item 81-84)
    - Unidentified female, "The Only Electra", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 85)
    - Charles Wartenberg, standing by large barrel, gymnast?, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 86)
    - Sisters Ethair, acrobats, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 8, Item 87-88)
    - Unidentified family of cyclists (1 man, 1 boy, 2 women), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 89)
    - Professor Elliott, bicyclist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 90)
    - Harry Wentworth, clown, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 91)
      See no. 79.
    - Goldie Rhinehart, daughter of Madame Rhinehart, Champion Four-Horse Chariot Driver, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 92)
    - Mollie Brown, Famous Equestrienne, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 93)
    - Miss Addie Austin, Equestrienne, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 94)
    - Annie Carroll, Equestrienne, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 95)
    - James Robinson, Chamption Equestrian, and Mrs. Robinson, Master Clarence Robinson, Rider. Cooper and Bailey in Australia, 1876; 1 item (Box 8, Item 96)
    - Nat Austin, Shakespearean Clown, Court Jester, and Equestrian Director. Cooper and Bailey, 1876-1878; 2 items (Box 8, Item 97-98)
    - George Austin, Rider, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 99)
    - Ahlardo Loranda, Rider, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 8, Item 100)
    - Bud Gorman, Equestrian, Cooper and Bailey, Australia, 1876-1877; 1 item (Box 9, Item 101)
    - Miss Polly Lee (Mrs. Bud Gorman), Equestrienne, 1893; 2 items (Box 9, Item 102-103)
    - Princess Nanna (Mrs. W.D. Ament), mindreader, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 104)
    - Viola Allen, leading lady in "Hoodman Blind", 1887-1883; 1 item (Box 9, Item 105)
    - Kibble, "Lightning Military Drill Act", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 106)
    - Miss Katamirka, snake charmer, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 107)
    - Unidentified black female, snake charmer, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 108)
    - Zola Zolera, snake charmer, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 9, Item 109-110)
      See Box 4.
    - Barnello, "Man with the Breath of Fire", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 111)
    - Unidentified chimpanzee of G.R. Burns, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 112)
    - Christmas Greeting photo of Harmston & Sons, animal training act, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 113)
    - Leonard Lewis, clown, animal trainer with trained mule, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 9, Item 114-115)
    - "The B. Grand and G.L. Club": Smith, Euso, Gonzella (Capt.), Loyal, Maffid, Davenport; group of performers with Cooper and Bailey Shows in Australia, 1876-1877; 1 item (Box 9, Item 116)
    - Unidentified female, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 117)
    - Harry V. LaVan, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 118)
    - Fred S. LaVan, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 119)
    - Unidentified woman, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 9, Item 120-121)
    - Lewis Davenport, Chicago, 1897; 1 item (Box 9, Item 122)
    - Unidentified man, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 123)
    - Unidentified woman, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 124)
    - Unidentified woman, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 125)
    - Mrs. William Batcheler, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 126)
      See no. 40
    - William George M. Thomson, 1885; 1 item (Box 9, Item 127)
    - Jessie Leon (woman), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 128)
    - Unidentified woman, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 129)
    - Nellie H. Venoa, Barnum and London Show, 1884; 1 item (Box 9, Item 130)
    - Oscar Lowande, child, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 131)
    - Fling, Jeal Ryland, Barnum Circus, 1884; 1 item (Box 9, Item 132)
    - Edward Walhaller, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 133)
    - William O'Dale Stevens, 1854-1883; 1 item (Box 9, Item 134)
    - George of Ziegler Bros, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 135)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Stints, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 136)
    - Nettie Stints, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 137)
    - Flora Stints, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 138)
    - Kennedy Family; W.B., Josie, Mexis, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 139)
    - Unidentified woman, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 140)
    - Unidentified man, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 9, Item 141-142)
    - Mr. Cross, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 143)
    - Alex C. Butler, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 144)
    - Edward Shipp, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 145)
    - Unidentified woman, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 146)
    - Unidentified man; composite, novelty photo (Large head, tiny body), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 147)
    - Unidentified female, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 148)
    - Matt Leland, 1880, or Joe M. Bailey, 1 item (Box 9, Item 149)
    - Miss Lee, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 150)
    - Unidentified man, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 151)
    - Miss Reed, daughter of Charles Reed, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 152)
    - Another Miss Reed, daughter of Charles Reed, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 153)
    - Goldie (young girl), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 154)
    - George Middleton, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 155)
    - Photo of Molly Brown, Equestrienne, and Linda Jeal, Rider and Juggler, on Christmas, care from the historian of the Circus Falls Association, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 156)
    - Fragment of program, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 157)
    - Postcard; The Great Florenz Troupe, acrobats, tumbles, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 9, Item 158)
    - Postcard; Barnum and Bailey, the Greatest Show on Earth, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 9, Item 159-160)
  - Animal Acts, 1876-1902 June 11; 2 boxes
    - Miss Milli Carlota, "Lion Queen", lion tamer, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 10, Item 1-2)
    - Idola, "The Lion Queen", lion tamer, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 3)
    - Unidentified woman, animal trainer, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 4)
    - Unidentified woman, animal trainer, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 5)
    - Carlota Aufman, animal trainer, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 6)
    - Unidentified woman, animal trainer, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 7)
    - Unidentified woman, animal trainer, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 8)
    - Unidentified woman, equestrienne, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 9)
    - Miss Mollie Brown, American Equestrienne, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 10)
      See Box 3, no. 93
    - Miss Nellie Burke, equestrienne, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 11)
    - Unidentified woman, equestrienne, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 12)
    - Unidentified woman, equestrienne, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 13)
    - "Barnum & Bailey Circus Girl" postcard of girl standing on horseback, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 14)
    - Unidentified woman, equestrienne, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 15)
    - Mari Dore, Equestrienne, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 16)
    - Unidentified woman, equestrienne, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 17)
    - Unidentified woman, equestrienne, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 10, Item 18-19)
    - Mrs. "Jenny T--y?", dates not examined; 3 items (Box 10, Item 20-22)
      See no. 42 for identif
    - Col. E. Daniel Boone, equestrian, dates not examined; 3 items (Box 10, Item 23-25)
    - William Oxford, Champion English Jockey, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 10, Item 26-27)
      See Box 1, nos. 54, 55.
    - Unidentified male, equestrian, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 28)
    - Bud Gorman, Equestrian, Cooper and Bailey Shows, Australia, 1876-1877; 1 item (Box 10, Item 29)
      See Box 9, no. 101.
    - C.F. Galetti, dog and monkey trainer, with chimp performance (a rope trick), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 30)
    - Two monkeys and a dog, in costume, performing tricks of "Galetti's Monkeys and Dogs, the Trained Animal Sensation", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 31)
    - "Willie Ketchum and his Trotting Dog, 'Doc'", dates not examined; 3 items (Box 10, Item 32-34)
    - Unidentified woman directing performing dog, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 35)
    - "Young Resps", Dirk Herbert's dog, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 36)
    - "Sancho", Madden's talking dog, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 37)
    - "Mom Bushnell's Imported Miniature Dogs", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 38)
    - "Tony, The American Dollar Dog", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 39)
    - "Wonderful Dog, Carl", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 40)
    - "Jack, the Only Somersault Dog in the World", trained and directed by Fred Watson, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 41)
    - Mrs. J---y and Admiral, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 10, Item 42)
      See nos. 20-22
    - Unidentified trainer, and "mathematical" horse, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 43)
    - Robert Whittaker, equestrian, atop horse, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 11, Item 44-45)
    - Robert Whittaker?, mounted, with another horse on rein, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 46)
    - Unidentified man holding a dappled horse on each side, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 47)
    - Postcard depicting Barnum and Bailey's equestrian segment, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 48)
    - Pinto saddle and driving horse, property of T. McCaddon, 1893; 1 item (Box 11, Item 49)
    - Pinto saddle and driving horse, and pony, held by unidentified man, property of T. McCaddon, 1893; 1 item (Box 11, Item 50)
    - "Mollie Silvermane", draft horse with flaxen mane to ground, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 51)
    - "My My", palomino horse, held by Mr. Stevenson, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 52)
    - "King Wilkes" stud, owner R.B. Conklin, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 53)
    - Destroyed horses following train wreck, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 54)
    - Mr. Carlo Thierbandiger, lion and tiger trainer, with four lions and one tiger, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 55)
    - Bull, hitched to cart, with four black children, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 56)
    - Bull with man, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 57)
    - "Beauty", Jersey red cow, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 58)
    - Grade Hereford Steer, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 59)
    - "Beauty, the Chick-rearing Cat", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 60)
    - Unidentified man holding two reindeer, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 61)
    - Prof. Woodward's Educated Seals and Sea Lions, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 62)
    - Siberian Camels, Hamburg, Germany, 1898. J.A. Bailey purchased four, 1 item (Box 11, Item 63)
    - "Fritz" (stuffed), died at Tours, 1902 June 11 (elephant), 1 item (Box 11, Item 64)
    - "Fritz", dead, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 65)
    - "Hebe", and baby "Young America", first elephant born in captivity Cooper and Bailey, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 66)
    - "Jumbo" and keeper, Scott, Barnum Circus, at Regent Park Zoo, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 67)
    - Unidentified elephant, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 68)
    - Dup. of no. 67, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 69)
    - Death of "Jumbo", dates not examined; 2 items (Box 11, Item 70-71)
      See Tuftonian article in special box
    - "Hebe" and "Young America", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 72)
      See no. 66
    - Barnum and Bailey Elephants testing new bridge at Bridgeport, CT., dates not examined; 1 item (Box 11, Item 73)
  - "Freaks," etc., 1898-1899; 2 boxes; 8 items
    - Midgets and Dwarves, dates not examined; 1 item
    - Lucia Zarate, "The Mexican Liliputian", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 12, Item 1)
    - Princess Topaze, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 12, Item 2)
    - Unidentified female midget, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 12, Item 3)
    - same as no. 3, with unidentified man, dates not examined; 3 items (Box 12, Item 4-6)
    - same as no. 3, with unidentified woman, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 12, Item 7)
    - Che Mark, Chinese dwarf, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 12, Item 8)